[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "From what you've been hearing, Ed, from your sources, consistent with everything that is now building up about the reality of the horror that went on in that house?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "you", "'ve", "been", "hearing", ",", "Ed", ",", "from", "your", "sources", ",", "consistent", "with", "everything", "that", "is", "now", "building", "up", "about", "the", "reality", "of", "the", "horror", "that", "went", "on", "in", "that", "house", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "That does go along with the fact that I'm hearing that Ariel Castro had a hierarchy.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "does", "go", "along", "with", "the", "fact", "that", "I", "'m", "hearing", "that", "Ariel", "Castro", "had", "a", "hierarchy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "What do you make of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, I'm hearing from the interrogation that he really didn't deny anything, but he didn't admit it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "hearing", "from", "the", "interrogation", "that", "he", "really", "did", "n't", "deny", "anything", ",", "but", "he", "did", "n't", "admit", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "I mean, this is a defense that's going to be extremely difficult to sustain itself, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "this", "is", "a", "defense", "that", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "extremely", "difficult", "to", "sustain", "itself", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "What was your reaction, when you first heard that Ariel Castro, the father of the man that you were married to, had been arrested in connection with this awful crime, series of crimes, what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", ",", "when", "you", "first", "heard", "that", "Ariel", "Castro", ",", "the", "father", "of", "the", "man", "that", "you", "were", "married", "to", ",", "had", "been", "arrested", "in", "connection", "with", "this", "awful", "crime", ",", "series", "of", "crimes", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I was shocked.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "shocked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "What kind of man -- what kind of man was he?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "man", "--", "what", "kind", "of", "man", "was", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", ":", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "I never had the desire to get to know him personally or very closely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "had", "the", "desire", "to", "get", "to", "know", "him", "personally", "or", "very", "closely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "And he also beat your ex-husband repeatedly when he was younger, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "also", "beat", "your", "ex-husband", "repeatedly", "when", "he", "was", "younger", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "What was the experience of being in that house with Ariel Castro like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "experience", "of", "being", "in", "that", "house", "with", "Ariel", "Castro", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "It's much like everyone else describes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "much", "like", "everyone", "else", "describes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ariel Castro"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Have you talked to your ex-husband since the revelations of a week ago?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "talked", "to", "your", "ex-husband", "since", "the", "revelations", "of", "a", "week", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Did you believe them when you saw their interview?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "believe", "them", "when", "you", "saw", "their", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Do you think the scale of what he was doing even then warranted more attention?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "the", "scale", "of", "what", "he", "was", "doing", "even", "then", "warranted", "more", "attention", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Oh, well, definitely, but I mean, I wish they had, but I can see how perhaps not.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "well", ",", "definitely", ",", "but", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "wish", "they", "had", ",", "but", "I", "can", "see", "how", "perhaps", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "Did you know her?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "But you never encountered her?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "never", "encountered", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "I don't believe so, or if I did, it wasn't in any, you know, lasting capacity.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "believe", "so", ",", "or", "if", "I", "did", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "in", "any", ",", "you", "know", ",", "lasting", "capacity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What is your overriding reaction?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "overriding", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "Just anguish.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "anguish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Dana, this is a right old mess for the president, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Dana", ",", "this", "is", "a", "right", "old", "mess", "for", "the", "president", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "That's certainly one way to put it.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "certainly", "one", "way", "to", "put", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Now, where and how is that line drawn, and how far over it from this report do we think they crossed?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "where", "and", "how", "is", "that", "line", "drawn", ",", "and", "how", "far", "over", "it", "from", "this", "report", "do", "we", "think", "they", "crossed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "That's absolutely right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "absolutely", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Has the White House handled this properly, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "the", "White", "House", "handled", "this", "properly", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Well, maybe B-plus but I'm mystified by the legalistic language.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "maybe", "B-plus", "but", "I", "'m", "mystified", "by", "the", "legalistic", "language", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Is it really feasible, do you think, that the IRS would independently be so overtly political against the Republicans and Tea Party in particular without anybody at the White House having at least had a quiet word?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "really", "feasible", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "that", "the", "IRS", "would", "independently", "be", "so", "overtly", "political", "against", "the", "Republicans", "and", "Tea", "Party", "in", "particular", "without", "anybody", "at", "the", "White", "House", "having", "at", "least", "had", "a", "quiet", "word", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS", "Tea Party", "White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "Should there be proof that emerges that somebody at the White House knew that the IRS were targeting the Tea Party and so on, how serious would that be?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "there", "be", "proof", "that", "emerges", "that", "somebody", "at", "the", "White", "House", "knew", "that", "the", "IRS", "were", "targeting", "the", "Tea", "Party", "and", "so", "on", ",", "how", "serious", "would", "that", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "First of all, I think it's a crime.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "crime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "IRS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eric Holder"]}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Does that in itself justify what they did in terms of basically going after the Associated Press and potentially checking the records of up to 100 journalists?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "in", "itself", "justify", "what", "they", "did", "in", "terms", "of", "basically", "going", "after", "the", "Associated", "Press", "and", "potentially", "checking", "the", "records", "of", "up", "to", "100", "journalists", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, full disclosure, I'm not only a friend but a great admirer of Eric Holder's for many, many years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "full", "disclosure", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "only", "a", "friend", "but", "a", "great", "admirer", "of", "Eric", "Holder", "'s", "for", "many", ",", "many", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Associated Press"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "And I suppose it really comes down to was what they did actually legal?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "suppose", "it", "really", "comes", "down", "to", "was", "what", "they", "did", "actually", "legal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, there is a ground for subpoenaing documents.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "is", "a", "ground", "for", "subpoenaing", "documents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA", "State Department"]}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "And I think they have a right to do that, don't they?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "they", "have", "a", "right", "to", "do", "that", ",", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, they certainly did remove those references, whether they were removed by the CIA or whether they were removed by people in the State Department is unclear.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "certainly", "did", "remove", "those", "references", ",", "whether", "they", "were", "removed", "by", "the", "CIA", "or", "whether", "they", "were", "removed", "by", "people", "in", "the", "State", "Department", "is", "unclear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Why not communicate that right up front?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "communicate", "that", "right", "up", "front", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "I agree with you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "JJS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "I think you put it all together with the IRS targeting the Tea Party, the Benghazi issue of these talking points and al Qaeda references being removed, the A.P. being targeted by the Justice Department, in what many consider to be an outrageous manner -- you put it all together, and you have a real breach of trust in President Obama and his administration, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "put", "it", "all", "together", "with", "the", "IRS", "targeting", "the", "Tea", "Party", ",", "the", "Benghazi", "issue", "of", "these", "talking", "points", "and", "al", "Qaeda", "references", "being", "removed", ",", "the", "A.P.", "being", "targeted", "by", "the", "Justice", "Department", ",", "in", "what", "many", "consider", "to", "be", "an", "outrageous", "manner", "--", "you", "put", "it", "all", "together", ",", "and", "you", "have", "a", "real", "breach", "of", "trust", "in", "President", "Obama", "and", "his", "administration", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "So look, yes, there's a breach of trust because of the opaqueness of the way the White House has handled it, at least starting with the talking points.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "look", ",", "yes", ",", "there", "'s", "a", "breach", "of", "trust", "because", "of", "the", "opaqueness", "of", "the", "way", "the", "White", "House", "has", "handled", "it", ",", "at", "least", "starting", "with", "the", "talking", "points", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IRS", "Tea Party", "Justice Department"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi", "A.P."], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "That eliminates a lot of people, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "eliminates", "a", "lot", "of", "people", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "It can.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Is that one of the wonders of modern science, if you like?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "one", "of", "the", "wonders", "of", "modern", "science", ",", "if", "you", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130514pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Just one last question, Dr. Sussman: do you believe, from your medical perspective, that this simple op-ed piece and the worldwide reaction can save a lot of lives?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "one", "last", "question", ",", "Dr.", "Sussman", ":", "do", "you", "believe", ",", "from", "your", "medical", "perspective", ",", "that", "this", "simple", "op-ed", "piece", "and", "the", "worldwide", "reaction", "can", "save", "a", "lot", "of", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I think she did tremendous goodwill and good work on behalf of women worldwide.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "did", "tremendous", "goodwill", "and", "good", "work", "on", "behalf", "of", "women", "worldwide", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Sussman"]}}]